Guide to the Metropolitan Council on Housing Records TAM.173
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: 2008 Accretion, 1951-2005; 84488; 8 Linear Feet
  - Rent Stabilization Association, 1991-1994; 84681 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Runyon, Marie, 1975-1976; 84680 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Schechter, Howard, 1986; 84679 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Scott, Walter, undated; 84678 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Starr, Roger, 1970-1985; 84677 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Stringer, Scott, 1994; 84676 (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - Tucker, William, 1989; 84675 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - Vallone, Peter, 2001; 84674 (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - Velella, Guy, undated; 84673 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - ACORN, 1986; 84672 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Action Council of Tenants for Yonkers, 1985-1986; 84671 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Action for Community Empowerment, 1992-1993; 84670 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Adopt a Building, 1970-1978; 84669 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Albany, 1996; 84668 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Asian Americans for Equality, 1987-1988; 84667 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Battery Park City, 1963-1978; 84666 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Chelsea, 1978-1992; 84665 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Coalition Against Rent Increase, 1982-2005; 84664 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Coalition to Save Lincoln Center Home for Senior Citizens, 1983; 84663 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Convention Center, 1973-1977; 84662 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Co-op City, 1965-1976; 84661 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Co-op City, 1979; 84660 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Co-op/Condo Conversion, 1975-1991; 84659 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1962-1995; 84658 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - East Harlem, 1984-1989; 84657 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Ebbets Field Tenants Action Council, 1964-1986; 84656 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act (I), 1974-1989; 84655 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Emergency Tenant Protection Act (II), 1974-1984; 84654 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Franklin Plaza, 1962-1968; 84653 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Glen Oaks Tenants Associations, 1981-1986; 84652 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Housing Policy, 1961-1971; 84651 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Lower East Side, 1982-2001; 84650 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Lower East Side Joint Planning Council, 1982-1986; 84649 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Lower Manhattan Expressway, 1962-1963; 84648 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Mandatory Rent Deposit, 1995; 84647 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Manhattan Valley Spanish Civic Organization, 1964-1966; 84646 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Rent Controlled Equalized Assessed Valuation, 1969-1974; 84645 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Rent Control Exemptions for Elderly, 1973-1979; 84644 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Rent Control New York State Committee Living Costs and The Economy, 1973; 84643 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Rent Control Outside New York City (I), 1977-1978; 84642 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Rent Control Outside New York City (II), 1978-1979; 84641 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Rent Control Outisde New York City (III), 1975-1988; 84640 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Rent Control Outside New York City (IV), 1973-1979; 84639 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Rent Controls (I), 1978-1989; 84638 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Rent Controls (II), 1989-1991; 84637 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Rent Guidelines, 1981; 84636 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Rent Regulations, 1987-2002; 84635 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1982-1997; 84634 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Rent Stabilization Clippings, 1968-2002; 84633 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Rent Stabilization Westchester, 1975-1997; 84632 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Seward Park Extension, 1968-1988; 84631 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - Tax Prop, 1975-1981; 84630 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Two Bridges, 1972-1973; 84629 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - West Side Housing Forum, 1996; 84628 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - West Village, 1963-1975; 84627 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - 7-A, 1970-1971; 84626 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Abandonment, 1969-1994; 84625 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Arson, 1978-1982; 84624 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Artists Housing, 1964-1988; 84623 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1965; 84622 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Benedict, Jane, 1984; 84621 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Boerum Hill, 1966-1976; 84620 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Brighton Beach, 1966-1974; 84619 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Bronx Crisis Coalition, 1970-1971; 84618 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Brooke Amendment, 1973; 84617 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Brooklyn Bridge, 1964-1965; 84616 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Equal, 1971; 84615 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Brownsville, 1961-1969; 84614 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Coney Island, 1969-1970; 84613 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - East New York, 1965-1989; 84612 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Flatbush, 1984; 84611 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Fort Greene, 1968-1969; 84610 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Harlem, undated; 84609 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Infestation/Mold, 2000-2003; 84608 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Met Council Internal, 1966-2003; 84607 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Fliers, 1972-2002; 84606 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Reports/Newsletters, undated; 84605 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Tenants Associations, 1997-2007; 84604 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Mitchell-Lama, 1984-2003; 84603 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - New York Is Our Home, 2007; 84602 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Northside Brooklyn (Williamsburg, Greenpoint), undated; 84601 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Paerdegat Basin, 1964; 84600 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Park Slope, 1975-1985; 84599 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Parkway-Stuyvesant-Community Life, 1961-1966; 84598 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Rent Control Canada, 1985; 84597 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Rent Stabilization (Early Years), 1969-1978; 84596 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Security, 1985-1987; 84595 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Security Deposit, 1968-1978; 84594 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Senior Housing, 1970-2003; 84593 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Senior Housing, 1962-1963; 84592 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Sheepshead Bay Focus Public Housing Abandonment, 1965-1966; 84591 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - South Bronx, 1974; 84590 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - SRO, 1989-1991; 84589 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - SRO, 1970-2001; 84588 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Subleasing, 1983-1986; 84587 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Succession Rights, 1985-1992; 84586 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Tenants and Neighbors, 1995-2003; 84585 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Vacancy Decontrol, 1971-1987; 84584 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Welfare, 1978-1985; 84583 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Where the Money Can Come From, 1984; 84582 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Where They Come From, Where They Go, 1973-1977; 84581 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Window Gates/Guards, 1986; 84580 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Zoning, 1970-1979; 84579 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Assoication of Neighborhood Housing Developers, 1982-1988; 84578 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Budger and code Enforcement, 1993-1998; 84577 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - City Planning, 1960-1966; 84576 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Code Enforcement, 1968-1969; 84575 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Code Enforcement, 1971-1978; 84574 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Code Enforcement, 1976-1990; 84573 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Con Edison, 1974-1976; 84572 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Con Edison, 1977; 84571 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Con Edison, 1977-1979; 84570 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1970-1975; 84569 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1978-1979; 84568 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1980; 84567 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1980-1982; 84566 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1981-1982; 84565 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Co-op Conversion (I), 1984-1985; 84564 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Co-op Conversion (II), 1984-1985; 84563 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Co-op Conversion, 1986-1987; 84562 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Co-op/Condo, 1987-1989; 84561 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Emergency Repair Program, 1974-1975; 84560 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Gay Rights, 1971-1989; 84559 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Gentrification, 1980-1999; 84558 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Harassment, 1970-1997; 84557 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Hardship, 1991; 84556 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Heat, 1980-1984; 84555 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Heat, 1986-1987; 84554 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Homelessness in New York City, 1982-1989; 84553 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Hospital Expansion, 1971-1972; 84552 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Hot Water, 1979-1985; 84551 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Hotels, 1982-1986; 84550 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Hotels, 1983-1985; 84549 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Lead, 1999; 84548 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Lead, 1999-2000; 84547 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Lead Legislation Letters, 1998-2004; 84546 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Lead Paint, 1983-1994; 84545 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - Lead Paint, 1996-1998; 84544 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Lead Paint, 1997; 84543 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Lead Paint, 1997-2000; 84542 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Lead Paint, 2000-2003; 84541 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Major Capital Improvements, 1980-1988; 84540 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Major Capital Improvements, 1987; 84539 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Major Capital Improvements, 1989-1992; 84538 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Major Capital Improvements (I), 1990; 84537 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Major Capital Improvements (II), 1990; 84536 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - 8A Loan, 1980-1987; 84535 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Bellevue, 1964-1967; 84534 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn Arms, 1989; 84533 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Commodore Hotel, 1976; 84532 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Displacement, 1988-2001; 84531 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1973-1984; 84530 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1985; 84529 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1986; 84528 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1986-1987; 84527 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1988-1989; 84526 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1990-1992; 84525 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1991; 84524 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal (I), 1991-1992; 84523 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal (II), 1991-1992; 84522 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, undated; 84521 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 2000-2003; 84520 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Drugs, 1987-1991; 84519 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Drugs, 1989-1990; 84518 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Dry Cleaners, 1993-1997; 84517 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Economics of Real Estate, 1974-1983; 84516 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Foreclosure, 1973-1992; 84515 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Freddie Mac, 1988-1992; 84514 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Garden Apartments, 1979-1986; 84513 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1968-1982; 84512 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1977-1979; 84511 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Housing Initiative, 1985-1986; 84510 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Incinerators, 1971; 84509 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Intercoms, Bells, Buzzers, 1967-1968; 84508 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Koch, Ed, 1977-1978; 84507 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Koch, Ed, 1981-1984; 84506 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, 1982; 84505 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - National People's Action, 1975-1982; 84504 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Network Magazine, 1977; 84503 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - People's Firehouse, 1982-1987; 84502 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Planners for Equal Opportunity, 1967-1971; 84501 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Redlining, 1962-1977; 84500 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Redlining, 1974; 84499 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Redlining, 1977-1979; 84498 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Rent Laws, 1993-1999; 84497 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1990; 84496 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1991; 84495 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1992; 84494 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1993-1994; 84493 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Rent Stabilization, 1994; 84492 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Settlement Housing Fund, 1978; 84491 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Tenants Rights, 1973-1975; 84490 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Union of City Tenants, 1985-1988; 84489 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Series V: 2014 Accretion, 1957-2014; 593127; 17 Linear Feet
  This series contains records related to housing rights campaigns of the Metropolitan Council on Housing, mostly from the late 1990s and the early 2000s. A large portion of these materials relate to rent laws and include files on individual building campaigns; the Rent Guidelines Board (RGB); copies of federal, state, and municipal regulations; and newspaper clippings related on housing rights activism. Other materials focus specifically topics affecting individual tenants and tenant demographics, which include Housing Vacancy Surveys, and files on Disability Rent Increase Exemptions (DRIE) and Senior Citizen Rent Increase Exemptions (SCRIE). A small amount of the records relate to the history of the Metropolitan Council on Housing and include a copy of the FBI's surveillance file on the organization. Other materials include an assortment of pamphlets and reports on housing and housing rights in New York City. These reports date from the 1950s to the early 2000s. Scattered throughout these boxes are several folders of materials related to the memorial of Met Council founder Jane Benedict, who died in 2005. These materials include her programs from her memorials service, biographical sketches of Benedict and correspondence and ephemera related to the memorial.
  The series also contains one box of Metropolitan Council on Housing photographs and publication mocks. The majority of the photographs document events like housing rights campaigns, demonstrations, meetings, and banquets. Others depict housing issues in the New York City including photographs of buildings, neighborhood, homeless shelters, and apartments. Photographs were most likely collected and created for use in issues of the Metropolitan Council on Housing's newspaper Tenant. Mockups mostly consist of photograph layouts and date from the 1970s to 1988.
  This series also contains issues of the Met Council's newspaper, Tenant, and copies of other periodicals related to housing rights including Tenant News and New York Apartment Law Insider. Copies of Tenant are mostly complete, and date from 1971 to 2014.
  - Met Council Photographs and Publication Mock-ups, 1960-1988; 593391 (Box 56)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Tenant Organizing, 1975-2006; 593392 (Box 57, Box 56)
  - Rent Laws: Federal State and Municipal Regulations, 1977-2001; 593393 (Box 58, Box 57)
  - Rent Laws: Rent Guidelines Board (RGB), 1990-2003; 593394 (Box 58)
  - Rent Laws: Campaigns and Demonstrations, 1997-2003; 593395 (Box 59)
  - Rent Laws: Building Campaigns, 1995-2005; 593396 (Box 60, Box 59)
  - Tenant Organizing: Housing Vacancy Surveys and Housing Studies, 1987-2006; 593397 (Box 60, Box 61)
  - Tenant Organizing: Rent Reform Campaigns and Rent Guidelines Board Advocacy, 2006-2009; 593398 (Box 62)
  - Tenant Organizing: Guidebooks and Educational Resources, 2003-2014; 593399 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing FBI File, 1957-1963; 593403 (Box 63)
  - Housing Studies, 1957-1971; 593400 (Box 64)
  - New York Apartment Law Insider, 2003-2010; 593401 (Box 64)
  - Tenant News, 1963-1968; 593404 (Box 64)
  - Housing Rights Handbooks and Metropolitan Council on Housing Pamphlets and Ephemera, 1964-1991; 593402 (Box 65)
  - Tenant, Metropolitan Council on Housing, 1971-2014; 593405 (Box 67, Box 68, Box 65, Box 66)
  - Exhibition Photographs for Jane Benedict Memorial, circa 2005; 593406 (Box MSXOS003, Folder 1)
  - Poster: "Protect Your Rights: Join Your Local Tenants Union", undated; 593407 (Box MSXOS003, Folder 2)
  - Award to Esther Rand: YCB Productions for the Excellent Quality of her Houisng Notebook, 1976 November; 593408 (Box C001)
- Series VI: Audio, 1978-1982; 478650; 1 Linear Feet
  Related Archival Materials
  Metropolitan Council on Housing audio materials that came to the repository between 2002 and 2007 can be found in Series III, box 27.
  The majority of the materials in this series are recordings of Jane Benedict's radio program "Tenants Fight For Survival," which was broadcast on WBLS.
  - Jane Benedict and Curti Truehart with Helen Cousin: Crown Heights (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero: Redemption Bill and Tenant Control (Side 2)., Jan 14, 1978 & Jan 24; 1978; 478879 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Ruth Steele: Mitchell-Lama Housing (Side 2)., Aug 6, 1978 & Aug, 13 1978; 478896 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Major Owens WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict, Juanita Nesbit, and Bess Stevenson on "In rem" and HPD. (Side 2)., Aug 20, 1978 & Aug 8, 1978; 478898 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict, Bess Stevenson, and Mrs. Ootine WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Assemblyman Frank Barbaro WBLS (Side 2)., Sep 3, 1978 & Sep 10, 1978; 478902 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Robert Marerro WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict with PKH on HPD: The Only Solution (Side 2)., Sep 17, 1978 & Sep 24, 1978; 478917 (Box 55)
  - WNYC: Special Report Guest Peter Hawley- Housing in the Public Domain, Sep 1978; 478918 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Peter K. Hawley (Part II): HPD (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart WBLS (Side 2)., Oct 1, 1978 & Oct 8, 1978; 478921 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict, Joe Hyler, Mrs. Gigliotti - re: 3681 Broadway WBLS (Side 1). Tom Granger and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 2)., Oct 15, 1978 & Oct 22 1978; 478865 (Box 55)
  - Jane Bendict, Mrs. Ghigliotti, Camacho; and Joe Hyler WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Tome Grainger (RENA) WBLS (Side 2)., Oct 15, 1978 & Oct 22, 1978; 478920 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart: Quincy Street, Crown Heights (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson WBLS (Side 2)., Nov 5, 1978 & Nov 12, 1978; 478919 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict, Andy Tate, and Cooper: LeFrack City [not a good recording] (Side 1). Jane Benedict and PKH: HDP Subsidized Housing, Mitchell-Lama, Manhattan Plaza (Side 2)., Nov 19, 1978 & Nov 26, 1978; 478912 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Bob Marerro WBLS; Dec 9 Conference and Brooklyn Court (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart: Arson (Side 2)., Dec 3, 1978 & Dec 10, 1978; 478906 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson: Settlement Housing Fund (Side 1). Jane Benedict solo WBLS (Side 2)., Dec 17, 1978 & Dec 24, 1978; 478903 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Bob Marerro: In rem etc. Part I (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Bob Marerro: In rem Part II (Side 2)., Dec 31, 1978 & Jan 7, 1979; 478892 (Box 55)
  - Jane Bendict and Miriam Friedlander: In rem (Side 1). Jane Benedict, Bob Marrero, and Katie Nichson: 2 Party checks, etc. (Side 2), Jan 28, 1979 & Feb 11, 1979; 478877 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict,Tom Grainger, and Mrs. Ghigliotti, Feb 2, 1979; 478873 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict (Solo) WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Major Owens WBLS (Side 2)., Feb 18, 1979 & Feb 25, 1979; 478871 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Katy Nichson WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict WBLS: Rent Controls and Legislation, Mar 4, 1979 & Mar 11, 1979; 478870 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero: Rent Control Hearings WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and William Moses of CHIP: "Let's Find Out" (Side 2)., Mar 18, 1979; 478869 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson- Rent Increases (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Robert Macrero- "Re in Rem" (Side 2)., Mar 25, 1979 & Apr 1, 1979; 478656 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Reverend Timothy Mitchell (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Chas Rangel (Side 2)., April 8, 1979 & April 22, 1979; 478864 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: How you can fight rising rents with Jane Benedict, Apr 15, 1979; 478868 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict, Apr 29, 1979; 478653 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict, May 6, 1979; 478655 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict with Lloyd Morris and Curtis Trueheart., May 13, 1979; 478654 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict-WBLS Labor Cost Repeal; Flynn-Dearie's Rent Guidelines (Side 1). Tenant Fight for Survival with guest Congressman Ted Weiss and Eng. Pat Johnon (Side 2)., May 27, 1979 & Jun 3, 1978; 478657 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero for WBLS re: Rent Guidelines (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero for WBLS re: Park West Village Victory and Warranty of Habitability (Side 2)., June 24, 1979 & Jul 1, 1979; 478724 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict with Arlene Francis WOR-AM, Jun 26, 1979; 478723 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson Parts 1 and 2., Jul 22, 1979 & Jul 29, 1979; 478722 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival; Jane Benedict and Bob Marrerro re: In Rem Before Board of Estimate (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Robert Marrero WBLS on Rent Increases (Side 2)., Aug 12, 1979 - Aug 19, 1979; 478857 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Jane Benedict and Bess Stevenson on Heat, Organizing, and Hearing, Aug 21, 1979; 478858 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict-WBLS (Side 1). Met Council Jim Haughton and Jane Benedict (Side 2)., Aug 27, 1979 & Sep 2, 1979; 478726 (Box 55)
  - WBLS Jane Benedict and Thomas Granges on In Row Houses (Side 1).Jane Benedict WBLS and Wilhemina Banks (Open Housing Center) (Side 2)., Sep 9, 1979 & Sep 16, 1979; 478826 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and William Moses of Community Housing Improvement Program (CHIP) WHN/Susan Dempsy "In the Public Interest" (Side 1)/ Jane Benedict and Robert Marrero WBLS- On Various Rent Hearings., Sep 16, 1979 & Sep 23, 1979; 478824 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict with LeFrak City representatives Richard Isles and David Washington (Side 1). Bob Marrero and Jane Benedict WBLS- Hearings and Tenant Unity Day (Side 2)., Sep 30, 1979 & Oct 7, 1979; 478825 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict on Tenant Unity Day etc. (Side 1). Nat Shapiro, Marty Bierbaum, Peter Hawlery on "Tenant Management" (Side 2)., Oct 14, 1979 & Oct 19, 1979; 478822 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict-WBLS (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Curtis Trueheart-WBLS (Side 2)., Oct 28,1979 & Nov 4, 1979; 478821 (Box 55)
  - WBLS 7AM-with Curtis Trueheart: Chevra Foundation (Side 1). Bob Marrero WBLS- Abandoned Housing (Side 2)., Nov 11, 1979 & Nov 18, 1979; 478721 (Box 55)
  - Apartment Living- WFDU-FM 98.1 Nat Shapiro and Pete K. Hawley, Nov 12, 1979 & Nov 23, 1979; 478820 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight #1: Jane Benedict and Bob Marerro- Don't Freeze (Side 1). Tenants Fight #2: Jane Benedict - Rents and Rent Guidelines (Side 2)., Dec 16, 1979 & Dec 23, 1979; 478831 (Box 55)
  - WBLS Jane Benedict and Nancy Biberman of MFY Legal Services- Rent Strike, Nov 25, 1979; 478829 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight #3, Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart - re: Crown Heights (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart - re: Section 236 rebates through HUD (Side 2)., Dec 30, 1979 & Jan 6, 1980; 478830 (Box 55)
  - WBLS Jane Benedict, Jan 13, 1980; 478832 (Box 55)
  - Tenants Fight for Survival: Tom Grauper and Jane Benedict - In rem Progress (Side 1). WBLS Tenants Survival: Willa Cummings (Bx. Baruch) and Jane Benedict (Side 2)., Jan 20, 1980 & Feb 10, 1980; 478836 (Box 55)
  - Tenant Fight: Bob Marrero and Jane Benedict - Fuel Cost Passalong (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival Bob Marrero and Jane Benedict - Fuel Cost Passalong and Oil Costs (Side 2)., Jan 27, 1980 & Feb 3, 1980; 478833 (Box 55)
  - Jane Benedict and Tom Granger - re: In rem to 495ft.; WBLS Jane Benedict and Curtis Truehart from 495ft. (Side 1). Jane Benedict and Burtis Trueheart and Committee of Brooklyn Avenue; Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero (Side 2)., Mar 9, 1980-Mar 30, 1980; 478839 (Box 55)
  - WBLS Katie Nichson (Harlem B.) and Jane Benedict, Mar 16, 1980; 478838 (Box 55)
  - Bess Stevenson and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival, Guest Bob Marrero (Side 2)., Apr 27, 1980 & Jul 6, 1980; 478840 (Box 55)
  - Bess Stevenson and Jane Benedict WBLS (Side 1). Tenants Fight for Survival- Jane Benedict and Bob Marrero, Apr 27, 1980 & Jul 6, 1980; 478842 (Box 55)